<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ronald Kato</title>
    <atom:link href="http://example.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <link>http://example.com/</link>
    <description>For the things we have to learn, we learn by doing them</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2015 22:30:03 +0200</pubDate>
    
      <item>
        <title>Up and running with Aurelia</title>
        <link>http://example.com/2015/08/01/Auerlia.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://example.com/2015/08/01/Auerlia.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://aurelia.io&quot;&gt;Aurelia&lt;/a&gt; is the latest incarnation from &lt;a href=&quot;http://eisenbergeffect.bluespire.com/&quot;&gt;Rob Eisenberg&lt;/a&gt;. If you have used &lt;a href=&quot;http://durandaljs.com/&quot;&gt;Durandal 2.0&lt;/a&gt; and liked it, then this may just be the framework for your next App. I really liked Durandal 2.0, and used it on two projects before I dove into Angular 1.x.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aurelia’s documentation is quiet good, as a walk through of the “getting started” section went without a hitch. Setting up a modern JavaScript App using &lt;a href=&quot;https://nodejs.org/&quot;&gt;Node.js&lt;/a&gt; and boostrapping a project with – &lt;a href=&quot;http://yeoman.io/&quot;&gt;Yeoman&lt;/a&gt; is really a breeze and if you have not tried it, you should give it a go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will be restructuring the default skeleton app to build a typical ecommerce app with the intention of pushing Aurelia to it’s limits. This should reveal all it’s capabilities. During this time I  will share my thoughts on the conventions of this framework, tasks such as routing, binding and templating. This should be fun and I will keep you posted.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Next-generation JavaScript Client Frameworks / Libraries</title>
        <link>http://example.com/2015/03/07/nextgen-js.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://example.com/2015/03/07/nextgen-js.html</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The landscape of JavaScript frameworks / libraries is changing fast. What started out as way to handle the DOM better through
declarative data binding has evolved into a competitive niche with Google and Facebook pitching contrasting
ideas and un expected collaborations – &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.msdn.com/b/typescript/archive/2015/03/05/angular-2-0-built-on-typescript.aspx&quot;&gt;a Angular 2 is built on TypeScript&lt;/a&gt;. So with ES6 on the horizon this is how it looking:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Angular 2.0&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Aurelia&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ember.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you are probably thinking where is React on that list. The guys at React say that it’s the V in MVC. But what does this mean for dynamic client UIs?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the next couple of posts, I will explore this landscape with the intention of gaining a better understanding of where we may be heading. All I can say now is that will all these options, it’s a great time to be a client side developer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
